**X**

Disable AdBlock!
================

You're using Ad Blocker.

Some features and activities may not work if you're using ad blocking software like AdBlock Plus.

Please whitelist Trust.Zone to continue.

Got itHow to Whitelist

**Special Deal** **Get 3-YEAR Plan for only $1.77/mo** [**Limited Offer** >>](https://trust.zone/post/missed-our-sale-here-is-62-off-coupon-code)

English

Your IP: 159.223.154.84 ·  United States ·

☰

[Why Trust.Zone?](https://trust.zone/trustzone-vpn)[Pricing](https://trust.zone/prices)[Setup VPN](https://trust.zone/setup)[Download](https://trust.zone/download)[Servers](https://trust.zone/servers)[Support](https://trust.zone/support)My Account

Privacy Policy
==============

The rules we hold about your Privacy
------------------------------------

We are privacy service and we realize how important it is that our customers fully understand what private information we collect, store and process. Our privacy policy goal is simple: maximizing your privacy.

### What information do we collect?

During registration of user we do collect user's email address. Email address is used as user's identifier, so user can login to the Trust.Zone account and receive notifications about subscription and promotions.

All 3rd parties Payments processors can store specific information about payments. You can track their privacy policy for more information during payment process. We do not save any personal details about the payments in our system.

### What information is logged when customers connect to our VPN service?

All our VPN servers around the world ARE NOT storing any log files to keep your privacy safe.

### Data Protection and Encryption

All public and private keys, account and VPN passwords are stored in encrypted format, using strong cryptographic algorithms. Appropriate security measures are taken for the protection of this information against unauthorized access, unauthorized alteration, destruction or disclosure of data.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service remember certain information). We store in cookies only some tech information about your current session after you logged in to our site. No personal information and emails stored in cookies.

### File Sharing Activities, DMCA Notices, illegal activities

You agree that you will not perform any kind of illegal file sharing activities and other illegal activities. Since our customers are anonymous when using our service, such notifications are reviewed by our team and an appropriate response is issued. Since we store no connection logs, we couldn't associate a request with a customer identity even if legally compelled to do so.

### Changes to policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on Dec, 24th 2018.

### Contact us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using [Contact page](https://trust.zone/contact "Contact us")

English

Home[Why Trust.Zone?](https://trust.zone/trustzone-vpn)[VPN Software](https://trust.zone/download)[Contact us](https://trust.zone/contact)[Servers](https://trust.zone/servers)[Support](https://trust.zone/support)[Terms of Service](https://trust.zone/terms)[Blog](https://trust.zone/blog)[Privacy Policy](https://trust.zone/privacy)[FAQ](https://trust.zone/faq)[Warrant Canary](https://trust.zone/canary)[Manual](https://trust.zone/manual)[Affiliate](https://get-trust-zone.info/)

### Latest News

#### 7 October, 2024 16:56:51

#### [Trust Zone - the best VPN with monthly price / confidentiality - according to Tom's HARDWARE](https://trust.zone/post/trustzone-the-best-vpn-with-monthly-price-confidentiality-in-france-according-to-tomshardware-fr)

Recently, the french edition of Tom's Hardware, the leading destination for...  

#### 28 September, 2024 12:31:34

#### [5 Reviews of Trust.Zone VPN from Tech Blogs](https://trust.zone/post/5-reviews-of-trust.zone-vpn-from-tech-blogs)

New reviews of Trust.Zone VPN service are appearing on the web!  We have...  

### Get Connected

Trust.Zone © 2024
